{'response_code': 0,
 'results': [{'category': 'Sports',
              'correct_answer': 'Horse-Riding',
              'difficulty': 'easy',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Cycling', 'Swimming', 'Running'],
              'question': 'Which of the following sports is not part of the '
                          'triathlon?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Board Games',
              'correct_answer': 'Brown',
              'difficulty': 'easy',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Green', 'Yellow', 'Blue'],
              'question': 'In a standard game of Monopoly, what colour are the '
                          'two cheapest properties?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Art',
              'correct_answer': '2/2',
              'difficulty': 'medium',
              'incorrect_answers': ['4/4', '6/8', '3/4'],
              'question': 'Which time signature is commonly known as '
                          '&ldquo;Cut Time?&rdquo;',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'History',
              'correct_answer': 'True',
              'difficulty': 'hard',
              'incorrect_answers': ['False'],
              'question': 'Japan was part of the Allied Powers during World '
                          'War I.',
              'type': 'boolean'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Film',
              'correct_answer': 'T-800',
              'difficulty': 'medium',
              'incorrect_answers': ['I-950', 'T-888', 'T-1000'],
              'question': 'In the 1984 movie &quot;The Terminator&quot;, what '
                          'model number is the Terminator portrayed by Arnold '
                          'Schwarzenegger?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Music',
              'correct_answer': 'Eddie Vedder',
              'difficulty': 'easy',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Ozzy Osbourne',
                                    'Stone Gossard',
                                    'Kurt Cobain'],
              'question': 'Who is the lead singer of Pearl Jam?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'History',
              'correct_answer': '500',
              'difficulty': 'medium',
              'incorrect_answers': ['100', '1000', '50'],
              'question': 'What number does the Roman numeral &quot;D&quot; '
                          'stand for?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Geography',
              'correct_answer': 'Kingston',
              'difficulty': 'easy',
              'incorrect_answers': ['San Juan', 'Port-au-Prince', 'Bridgetown'],
              'question': 'What is the capital of Jamaica?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'History',
              'correct_answer': 'Airship Dock',
              'difficulty': 'medium',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Lightning Rod', 'Antennae', 'Flag Pole'],
              'question': 'The crown of the Empire State Building was '
                          'originally built for what purpose?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Music',
              'correct_answer': 'True',
              'difficulty': 'easy',
              'incorrect_answers': ['False'],
              'question': 'Eurobeat is primarily an Italian genre of music.',
              'type': 'boolean'},
             {'category': 'Science & Nature',
              'correct_answer': '8',
              'difficulty': 'easy',
              'incorrect_answers': ['7', '9', '6'],
              'question': 'How many planets make up our Solar System?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'History',
              'correct_answer': '5%',
              'difficulty': 'medium',
              'incorrect_answers': ['1%', '3%', '&lt;1%'],
              'question': 'According to scholarly estimates, what percentage '
                          'of the world population at the time died due to '
                          'Tamerlane&#039;s conquests?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Video Games',
              'correct_answer': 'Mental Health Issues',
              'difficulty': 'hard',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Injuries', 'Disease', 'Danger to Others'],
              'question': 'Why was the character Trevor Philips discharged '
                          'from the Air Force?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Video Games',
              'correct_answer': 'x86 Assembly',
              'difficulty': 'medium',
              'incorrect_answers': ['C++', 'C', 'ALGOL'],
              'question': '&quot;Rollercoaster Tycoon&quot; was programmed '
                          'mostly entirely in...',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Music',
              'correct_answer': 'MGMT',
              'difficulty': 'medium',
              'incorrect_answers': ['MSTRKRFT', 'STRFKR', 'SBTRKT'],
              'question': 'Which of these is the name of an American '
                          'psychedelic rock band formed in 2002 by Benjamin '
                          'Goldwasser and Andrew VanWyngarden?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Geography',
              'correct_answer': 'Munich',
              'difficulty': 'medium',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Berlin', 'Hamburg', 'Dortmund'],
              'question': 'Which German city is located on the River Isar?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations',
              'correct_answer': 'Water',
              'difficulty': 'easy',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Air', 'Earth', 'Fire'],
              'question': 'In &quot;Avatar: The Last Airbender&quot;, which '
                          'element does Aang begin to learn after being '
                          'defrosted?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'General Knowledge',
              'correct_answer': 'Pomodoro',
              'difficulty': 'medium',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Aglio', 'Cipolla', 'Peperoncino'],
              'question': 'What is the Italian word for &quot;tomato&quot;?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Board Games',
              'correct_answer': 'True',
              'difficulty': 'easy',
              'incorrect_answers': ['False'],
              'question': 'The Angry Video Game Nerd&#039;s alter ego is '
                          '&quot;Board James&quot;.',
              'type': 'boolean'},
             {'category': 'Vehicles',
              'correct_answer': 'VANOS',
              'difficulty': 'hard',
              'incorrect_answers': ['VVT-iw', 'VVEL', 'MultiAir'],
              'question': 'Which Variable Valve Timing technology is used by '
                          'BMW?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'History',
              'correct_answer': '1995',
              'difficulty': 'hard',
              'incorrect_answers': ['2001', '2011', '1991'],
              'question': 'In which year did the Tokyo Subway Sarin Attack '
                          'occur?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Video Games',
              'correct_answer': 'Glass',
              'difficulty': 'medium',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Mirrors', 'Purity', 'Diamonds'],
              'question': 'Mirror&#039;s Edge Catalyst takes place in the City '
                          'of...?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Music',
              'correct_answer': 'Compton',
              'difficulty': 'hard',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Detroit', 'New York', 'Baltimore'],
              'question': 'In Kendrick Lamar&#039;s 2012 album, &quot;Good '
                          'Kid, M.A.A.D City&quot;, the album&#039;s story '
                          'takes place in which city?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Board Games',
              'correct_answer': 'Extreme Dungeons &amp; Dragons',
              'difficulty': 'easy',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Advanced Dungeons &amp; Dragons',
                                    'Dungeons &amp; Dragons 3.5th edition',
                                    'Advanced Dungeons &amp; Dragons 2nd '
                                    'edition'],
              'question': 'Which one of these is not a real game in the '
                          'Dungeons &amp; Dragons series?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Geography',
              'correct_answer': 'Brazil',
              'difficulty': 'easy',
              'incorrect_answers': ['China', 'Russia', 'The United States'],
              'question': 'Which country is the home of the largest Japanese '
                          'population outside of Japan?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Music',
              'correct_answer': 'Panic! At the Disco',
              'difficulty': 'easy',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Twenty One Pilots',
                                    'My Chemical Romance',
                                    'Fall Out Boy'],
              'question': 'In 2006, which band released their debut album '
                          '&quot;A Fever You Can&#039;t Sweat Out&quot;?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'General Knowledge',
              'correct_answer': 'Center Parcs',
              'difficulty': 'hard',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Yelloh Village', 'Keycamp', 'Villa Plus'],
              'question': 'De Eemhof, Port Zelande and Het Heijderbos are '
                          'holiday villas owned by what company?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Video Games',
              'correct_answer': 'A shell',
              'difficulty': 'hard',
              'incorrect_answers': ['A slide of Gelatin',
                                    'A poffin',
                                    'A spike'],
              'question': 'During development of &quot;Super Mario '
                          'World&quot;, Yoshi&#039;s hard saddle was '
                          'originally which of these?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'History',
              'correct_answer': 'False',
              'difficulty': 'medium',
              'incorrect_answers': ['True'],
              'question': 'Adolf Hitler was accepted into the Vienna Academy '
                          'of Fine Arts.',
              'type': 'boolean'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Video Games',
              'correct_answer': 'Counter-Strike 1.6',
              'difficulty': 'easy',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Half-Life',
                                    'Half-Life 2',
                                    'Team Fortress'],
              'question': 'What game was used to advertise Steam?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Television',
              'correct_answer': 'Grapok sauce',
              'difficulty': 'hard',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Gazorpazorp pudding',
                                    'Sweet chili sauce',
                                    'Grapork sauce'],
              'question': 'In &quot;Star Trek&quot;, what sauce is commonly '
                          'used by Klingons on bregit lung?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations',
              'correct_answer': 'Mason Pines',
              'difficulty': 'medium',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Mable Pines', 'Jason Pines', 'Mark Pines'],
              'question': 'What is Dipper&#039;s real name from &quot;Gravity '
                          'Falls&quot;?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Musicals & Theatres',
              'correct_answer': 'Brendon Urie',
              'difficulty': 'hard',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Ed Sheeren',
                                    'Tom Cruise',
                                    'Dallon Weekes'],
              'question': 'Who played &quot;Charlie Price&quot; in the musical '
                          '&quot;Kinky Boots&quot; on Broadway in New York '
                          'from May 26th - Aug 6th 2017?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Video Games',
              'correct_answer': 'Belushya Guba',
              'difficulty': 'medium',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Yasnaya Polyana', 'Pochinki', 'Georgopol'],
              'question': 'Which of these is NOT a name of a city in the main '
                          'island of PLAYERUNKNOWN&#039;S BATTLEGROUNDS?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Geography',
              'correct_answer': 'Vilnius',
              'difficulty': 'medium',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Tallinn', 'Helsinki', 'Riga'],
              'question': 'What is the capital of Lithuania?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Video Games',
              'correct_answer': 'Fonts',
              'difficulty': 'easy',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Plants',
                                    'Companies',
                                    'Ancient writing paper'],
              'question': 'What are Sans and Papyrus named after in '
                          '&quot;Undertale&quot;?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Video Games',
              'correct_answer': 'Scyther',
              'difficulty': 'hard',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Pikachu', 'Sneasel', 'Larvesta'],
              'question': 'What Pok&eacute;mon&#039;s Base Stat Total does not '
                          'change when it evolves?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Books',
              'correct_answer': 'The House Elf',
              'difficulty': 'easy',
              'incorrect_answers': ['The Chamber of Secrets',
                                    'The Prisoner of Azkaban',
                                    'The Deathly Hallows'],
              'question': 'Which is NOT a book in the Harry Potter Series?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Animals',
              'correct_answer': 'Portuguese Man-of-War',
              'difficulty': 'hard',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Sea Wasp', 'Irukandji', 'Sea Nettle'],
              'question': 'Which of these is a colony of polyps and not a '
                          'jellyfish?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Television',
              'correct_answer': 'The Joker',
              'difficulty': 'medium',
              'incorrect_answers': ['The Penguin', 'The Riddler', 'Mr. Freeze'],
              'question': 'Cesar Romero played which iconic Batman villain '
                          'from the 1960&#039;s TV show?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'History',
              'correct_answer': 'Mayans',
              'difficulty': 'hard',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Aztecs', 'Incas', 'Toltecs'],
              'question': 'The ancient city of Chich&eacute;n Itz&aacute; was '
                          'built by which civilization?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations',
              'correct_answer': 'The Slag Brothers',
              'difficulty': 'hard',
              'incorrect_answers': ['The Slate Brothers',
                                    'The Rock Brothers',
                                    'The Stone Brothers'],
              'question': 'In the 1968 Cartoon Show &quot;Wacky Races&quot; '
                          'what was the name of cavemen duo who rode in The '
                          'Boulder Mobile?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Books',
              'correct_answer': 'Friedrich Engels',
              'difficulty': 'hard',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Robert Owen',
                                    'Alexander Kerensky',
                                    'Paul Lafargue'],
              'question': 'Which author co-wrote &quot;The Communist '
                          'Manifesto&quot; alongside Karl Marx?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Science: Mathematics',
              'correct_answer': '1.58 x 10^20',
              'difficulty': 'hard',
              'incorrect_answers': ['1.58 x 10^22',
                                    '1.58 x  10^18',
                                    '1.58 x 10^24'],
              'question': 'Which of these numbers is closest to the total '
                          'number of possible states for an army standard '
                          'Enigma Machine?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Science: Mathematics',
              'correct_answer': 'John Von Neumann',
              'difficulty': 'hard',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Carl Friedrich Gauss',
                                    'Leonhard Euler',
                                    'Stefan Banach'],
              'question': 'Which of the following mathematicians made major '
                          'contributions to game theory?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Film',
              'correct_answer': 'John Travolta',
              'difficulty': 'easy',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Christoph Waltz',
                                    'Harvey Keitel',
                                    'Samuel L. Jackson'],
              'question': 'Which of the following actors has only been in a '
                          'Quentin Tarantino directed film once?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'History',
              'correct_answer': 'Australia',
              'difficulty': 'hard',
              'incorrect_answers': ['India', 'Canada', 'Brazil'],
              'question': 'Which country did the Eureka Rebellion, an 1856 '
                          'battle against colonial rule, take place in?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Music',
              'correct_answer': 'For Blood And Empire',
              'difficulty': 'easy',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Infinity On High',
                                    '21st Century Breakdown',
                                    'No Pads, No Helmets...Just Balls'],
              'question': 'Which of the following is an album by punk rock '
                          'band Anti-Flag?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Comics',
              'correct_answer': 'Spiral City',
              'difficulty': 'easy',
              'incorrect_answers': ['Mega-City One', 'Rockwood', 'Star City'],
              'question': 'In Black Hammer, what city did the heroes save from '
                          'the Anti-God?',
              'type': 'multiple'},
             {'category': 'Entertainment: Video Games',
              'correct_answer': 'October 31st, 2019',
              'difficulty': 'easy',
              'incorrect_answers': ['January 13th, 2019',
                                    'September 6th, 2018',
                                    'October 1st, 2019'],
              'question': 'When was &quot;Luigi&#039;s Mansion 3&quot; '
                          'released?',
              'type': 'multiple'}]}